<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="main_string">Bem-vindo ao AA AIO Tweaker\n
Este aplicativo permitirá que você aplique alguns ajustes no Android Auto\n
Basta selecionar o ajustes que você deseja aplicar :)\n
Se você não tem certeza do que faz um ajuste, toque longo nele e um tutorial será exibido.</string>
    <string name="select_apps">Selecione apps</string>
    <string name="enable_assistant_shortcuts">Atalhos da assistente</string>
    <string name="patch_custom_apps">apps Personalizados</string>
    <string name="disable_speed_limitations">limite de toques</string>
    <string name="unlimited_scrolling_when_driving">restrições de velocidade</string>
    <string name="message_auto_read">Message auto-read</string>
    <string name="splash">Este aplicativo pode alterar o comportamento automático do Android e ignorar alguns recursos de segurança que o Google implementou no Android Auto.\n
Ao usar este software, você concorda que VOCÊ e SOMENTE VOCÊ são os únicos responsáveis por qualquer possível consequência que pode resultar em alterar recursos de segurança, como ferimentos para você mesmo e/ou outros, danos à propriedade, perda de vida.\n
Sob nenhuma circunstância é o autor deste app responsável pela sua utilização</string>
    <string name="proceed">Estou ciente</string>
    <string name="navigation_at_start">Navegação no início</string>
    <string name="statb_opaque_string">Forçar Statusbar Opaca</string>
    <string name="battery_outline_string">contorno da economia de bateria</string>
    <string name="legend">Status Legend:\n
VERDE= Patch aplicado\n
AMARELO= Patch precisa ser reiniciado para ser aplicado\n
VERMELHO= Patch não é aplicável\n</string>
    <string name="set_notification_duration_to">Duração das notificações para</string>
    <string name="base_no_ws">Tela Cheia</string>
    <string name="force_widescreen_text">Forçar tela cheia</string>
    <string name="media_notification_duration_to">Duração das notificações de mídia para</string>
    <string name="bluetooth_auto_connect">Conectar Bluetooth automaticamente</string>
    <string name="tutorial_nospeed">Este ajuste fará o Android Auto pensar que o carro está em 0 velocidade. Como resultado, Android Auto sempre
    mostra a visualização das mensagens. Este ajuste não se aplica ao teclado ou à primeira configuração do Android Auto.</string>
    <string name="tutorial_sixtap">Este ajuste substituirá o limite de 6 toques do Android Auto e tornará sempre possível a navegação ilimitada do conteúdo.</string>
    <string name="tutorial_shortcuts">Esta opção irá desbloquear a nova função de Atalhos Assistentes. Uma vez ativado você pode ir nas configurações do Android Auto e na seção personalizada do launcher
    você pode começar a adicionar atalhos aos comandos do Google Assistente</string>
    <string name="tutorial_startup">This tweak will override the default behaviour of Android Auto opening a navigation app at start and will make Android Auto start on launcher.\n
This tweak could occasionally fail because sometimes Android Auto starts with a navigation to home or work autonomously. This behaviour breaks the tweak.\n
In some cases this tweak will disable auto start of music. A known workaround is to disable and re-enable the option within Android Auto settings.\n
IT\'S NOT POSSIBLE TO SET A SPECIFIC APP TO START FIRST.</string>
    <string name="tutorial_widescreen">Este ajuste irá forçar o Android Auto em modo de tela widescreen.</string>
    <string name="tutorial_no_widescreen">Este ajuste irá forçar o Android Auto em modo de tela sem widescreen.</string>
    <string name="tutorial_autoplay_message">This tweak enables the possibility to set whether Android Auto must read the incoming messages or not. Android Auto 8.3 or superior is required.</string>
    <string name="tutorial_statusbar_opaque">This tweak will make the status bar always with an opaque background (default is transparent)</string>
    <string name="tutorial_battery_outline">Este ajuste impedirá o ícone da bateria com o contorno vermelho quando a economia de bateria estiver ativada.</string>
    <string name="tutorial_hun">Este ajustes permite que você defina uma duração personalizada para notificações heads up</string>
    <string name="tutorial_media_hun">Este ajuste permite que você defina um período personalizado para as notificações de mídia na barra de navegação até 15 minutos.</string>
    <string name="tutorial_bluetooth">Este ajuste deve impedir que o Bluetooth seja ativado quando o Android Auto estiver conectado. Isto não funcionará se o Bluetooth já estiver ligado.</string>
    <string name="tutorial_patchapps">Esse \"truque\" irá habilitar aplicativos de terceiros feitos especificamente com o SDK modificado Android Auto.\n
Se você é familiar com o AA Phenotype Patcher, esse \"truque\" é quase idêntico com ele.\n
Não é possível adicionar qualquer app ao Android Auto, mas é possível adicionar aplicativos FEITOS PARA ANDROID AUTO para funcionar em carros.</string>
    <string name="multi_display_string">Visualização múltipla</string>
    <string name="tutorial_multidisplay">This is an hidden feature inside Android Auto that will turn the second space in widescreen mode to a real second display that is completely taken by another activity. Google Maps will display a full map with navigation status, music and phones will take the full space.\n
        Additionally, this mode activates another feature that will turn the phone\'s screen in a second display for navigation in Android Auto.\n
        Settings for tweaking this feature will be available in Android Auto homescreen.\n
        Apparently, only Google Maps currently support this mode.\n
        This feature is probably under development and could potentially not work as intended.\n
    Android Auto 5.8 or superior is required.</string>
    <string name="battery_warning">Aviso de Economia de bateria</string>
    <string name="tutorial_battery_saver_warning">Este ajuste irá impedir que o Android dê avisos popup quando o modo de economia de bateria estiver ativado</string>
    <string name="disable_tweak_string">Desativar\u0020</string>
    <string name="enable_tweak_string">Ativar\u0020</string>
    <string name="re_enable_tweak_string">Reativar\u0020</string>
    <string name="copy_log">Copiar log</string>
    <string name="about">Sobre</string>
    <string name="revert_everything">Reverter tudo</string>
    <string name="force_disable_tweak">Forçar Desativação\u0020</string>
    <string name="reset_tweak">Resetar\u0020</string>
    <string name="force_widescreen_warning">Forçar tela widescreen automaticamente foi desativado</string>
    <string name="force_disable_widescreen_warning">Forçar o desligamento da tela widescreen foi desativado automaticamente</string>
    <string name="set_value">Definir\u0020</string>
    <string name="reboot_to_apply">REINICIAR PARA APLICAR</string>
    <string name="warning_title">ATENÇÃO</string>
    <string name="unpatch">Desfazer a correção\u0020</string>
    <string name="patch_app">Corrigir\u0020</string>
    <string name="default_string">\u0020Padrão</string>
    <string name="app_list_label">Lista de aplicativos</string>
    <string name="translators_button">Traduzido por</string>
    <string name="custom_wallpapers">Papeis de parede</string>
    <string name="tutorial_wallpapers">Este ajuste ativará o novo seletor de papel de parede construído no Android Auto. Android Auto 5.8 ou superior é necessário.\nAVISO: Se você é um usuário de papéis de parede para Android Auto, precisará atualizá-lo para pelo menos a versão 3., Caso contrário, este ajustes irá quebrar papéis de parede para a funcionalidade do Android Auto.</string>
    <string name="tutorial_dark_mode">A partir de dezembro de 2020, a Google reverteu um comportamento que aconteceu desde o Android 10. Anteriormente, o modo claro/escuro no Android Auto seguiu o modo claro / escuro no telefone e vice-versa. Isto significava que a opção do telefone para o modo escuro teve efeito no carro, ou se o telefone estava em modo escuro e o carro tinha luzes apagadas para ligar o tema claro no telefone.\n No entanto, desde que esse recurso de modo \"independente\" foi introduzido, usuários com cabeças de pós-mercado não têm maneira de alternar para o modo escuro mais sem fazer fiação do estéreo para as luzes do carro.\n Este ajustes certifica-se de que o modo noturno é de novo dependente do telefone e ativar o modo claro/escuro no telefone também terá seus efeitos nos carros também.</string>
    <string name="dark_mode_tweak">modo escuro independente</string>
    <string name="telemetry_string">telemetria</string>
    <string name="tutorial_telemetry">It\'s no mystery that Google logs a lot of data about us. This tweak will make so that Google Play Services will stop a lot of tracking and logging activity.\n
WARNING: This tweak has not been extensively tested and could potentially break Android Auto. If you find out that this tweak breaks Android Auto, please open an issue on GitHub.</string>
    <string name="reboot_prompt">Reiniciar o dispositivo agora?</string>
    <string name="rebooting_action">Reiniciando…</string>
    <string name="added_app_action">"Added: "</string>
    <string name="removed_app_action">Removed\u0020</string>
    <string name="root_access_warning">Acesso root negado. Por favor, permita o acesso root.</string>
    <string name="revert_everything_dialog">Do you want to revert everything? Please manually restart the app after doing so</string>
    <string name="calendar_tweak">Set %1$s visible days in calendar</string>
    <string name="calendar_tweak_single">Set %1$s visible day in calendar</string>
    <string name="tutorial_calendar_tweak">This tweak will make so that calendar app into Android Auto can show more days than just one. Please note that even increasing the number of days, it\'s still not obviously possible to distinguish which day you are viewing the events of. Android Auto will just show how many events are set in one day and it won\'t show which day it is.</string>
    <string name="choose_apps_warning">Choose apps to whitelist</string>
    <string name="log_first_line">LOG:\n</string>
    <string name="menu_aa_settings">Open Android Auto settings</string>
    <string name="not_enabled_warning">Android Auto is not enabled</string>
    <string name="not_installed_warning">Android Auto is not installed</string>
    <string name="currently_set">"Currently set: "</string>
    <string name="no_accounts_warning">AA AIO TWEAKER could not find any account in Google Play Services database. This can be caused by several different things such as:\n • Device that is mostly not connected to internet\n • Fresh install of the phone\n • Corrupted Google Play Services database\n • Removal of Google account(s) from the phone\n • Cleared datas of Google Play Services\n\nIn this scenario, AA AIO TWEAKER will FAIL to work properly. If you recently removed a Google account or cleared Google Play Services datas, please keep the phone connected to internet and let it build the Google Play Services database fully. This might take several hours, in some cases also days.\n\nIf you are not in one of the above conditions, please open a issue on GitHub.</string>
    <string name="tweak_loading">Applying the tweak...</string>
    <string name="loading">Loading, please wait...</string>
    <string name="tutorial_bitrate">This tweak will increase or decrease video bitrate according to the multiplier set (up to 2.0x). Increasing the bitrate (more than 1.0x) will mean that more datas will be streamed to the car and quality of video streaming could be improved in visual quality, however it might cause instability. Decreasing the bitrate (less than 1.0x) will compress the stream to the car and quality will be decreased, but it will result in a more reliable and fast connection.</string>
    <string name="set_wifi_tweak">wifi bitrate to</string>
    <string name="set_usb_bitrate">USB bitrate to</string>
    <string name="choose_value_first">Choose a value first</string>
    <string name="open_issue_button">Open Issue</string>
    <string name="error_generic">The command was not successful. Please wait some minutes and try again. If problem is still ongoing, please open a issue on GitHub</string>
    <string name="tutorial_alphajump">This tweak will activate a new (and hidden) redesign that changes how lists can be browsed with letters. Instead of the A-Z button at the top, the button will appear on the scrollbar when there\'s no scroll happening and you won\'t be forced to go to top to browse with letters again.</string>
    <string name="alpha_jump_tweak">new alphabet jump</string>
    <string name="choose_accounts">Choose accounts</string>
    <string name="use_all">Use all (EXPERIMENTAL)</string>
    <string name="log_copied">Log has been copied</string>
    <string name="new_version_available">New Version available</string>
    <string name="go_to_new_version">A new version of AA AIO TWEAKER (version %1$s) is available on GitHub. Do you want to download it now?</string>
    <string name="go_to_download">Go to download</string>
    <string name="ignore_for_now">Ignore for now</string>
    <string name="many_accounts_warning">AA AIO TWEAKER found a large number (%1$s) of Google accounts saved in the device.\nThis can negatively impact on the success of the patching process and AA AIO TWEAKER might fail.\nYou can either choose the account(s) that you mostly use with Google Play Services to apply the patch to just them (2 or less is recommended) or activate an experimental mode that should patch all accounts.\nPLEASE NOTE that the experimental mode might cause some crashes to the phone while the patch is running.</string>
    <string name="dark_switch_tweak">day/night option</string>
    <string name="tutorial_assistant_suggestions">This tweak will activate a new feature that adds some quick shortcuts to Assistant actions on top of home screen.</string>
    <string name="remove_paired_car">Remove a paired car</string>
    <string name="choose_cars">Choose car(s)</string>
    <string name="tutorial_carremover">Did you know that you can only remove all the paired cars from Android Auto and you cannot remove just one at a time? This option will rescue you if you want to delete a car from Android Auto, just select which car(s) you want and it/they will be removed.</string>
    <string name="coolwalk_daynight_tweak">Light/Dark Coolwalk</string>
    <string name="coolwalk_daynight_tutorial">This tweak will activate day/night mode for Coolwalk mode. Looks kind of broken right now and can\'t handle switch very well.</string>
    <string name="custom_hotseat_option">Custom seating option</string>
    <string name="tutorial_coolwalk">This tweak will activate a new design in Android Auto (codename Coolwalk) that can be toggled in Android Auto\'s settings and that tweaks a bit the appearance on smaller screens. This design features a always on side panel and some different graphics. This feature is in early stage at the moment. Android Auto 6.9 or superior is required.</string>
    <string name="coolwalk_tweak">Coolwalk design</string>
    <string name="tutorial_focus_settings">Este ajuste ativará novas opções nas configurações do Android Auto para personalizar manualmente se o Android Auto deve ser iniciado assim que você conectar seu telefone ao carro. Android Auto 6.8 ou superior é necessário.</string>
    <string name="focus_tweak">Ajustes de Foco</string>
    <string name="assistant_tips">Assistant tips</string>
    <string name="tutorial_mirroring_app">This tweak will enable Assistant Tips on the top of the home screen for most used actions. Android Auto 8.2 or superior is required.</string>
    <string name="decline_message_tweak">Recusar com mensagem</string>
    <string name="tutorial_decline_message">This tweak will enable the possibility to decline an incoming call with SMS (with Google Assistant).</string>
    <string name="section_one">General tweaks</string>
    <string name="section_two">Screen setup tweaks</string>
    <string name="section_three">Appearance tweaks</string>
    <string name="section_four">Video quality settings</string>
    <string name="section_five">Pre-activate features</string>
    <string name="restricted_coolwalk">\nThis option will only work with Coolwalk enabled.</string>
    <string name="warning_patch_apps">Warning! This operation will ERASE ALL THE DATA from the selected app(s). Please make sure you have a backup of the data. Do you want to proceed anyways?</string>
    <string name="tappable_progress">New progress bar</string>
    <string name="tappable_progress_tutorial">Finally we are gaining a touchable progress bar for what\'s playing on Android Auto. Yes, we can seek through the current track Requires Android Auto 8.3 or superior.</string>
    <string name="uxprototype_tutorial">All this tweak does is basically creates a free shortcut on the home page to open a web page. It involves an Easter egg hidden in Android Auto released on 1st of April 2022. Activate \"Developer mode\" in \"Developer settings\" under \"Application mode\". It\'s the only way to have an actual fullscreen app on Android Auto right now. WARNING: Not exitable, use this if you only plan on using this on your car. There\'s no back button either.</string>
    <string name="uxprototype_dialog">Enter a valid full URL</string>
    <string name="uxprototype_tweak">Custom shortcut</string>
    <string name="tutorial_new_seekbar">"This tweak enables a movable seekbar for media apps."</string>
    <string name="tutorial_materialyou">"This tweak enables material you style for the Android Auto's settings on the phone. This properly works only on Android Auto 8.8&gt; as tested"</string>
    <string name="tutorial_nocoolwalk">Are you absolutely hating Coolwalk? This tweak is for you.</string>
    <string name="portrait_layout">Force vertical layout</string>
    <string name="tutorial_portrait">This tweak will force the portrait layout of Android Auto with dashboard on the bottom.</string>
    <string name="inertial_scroll_tweak">Inertial scroll</string>
    <string name="tutorial_inertial_scroll">This tweak will override the default scrolling behaviour of Android Auto making so that it doesn\'t stop page by page.</string>
</resources>
