<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="main_string">Velkommen i AA AIO Tweaker\n
Denne app vil lade dig anvende nogle tweaks til Android Auto\n
Vælg blot hvad tweak du ønsker at anvende :)\n
Hvis du er usikker på, hvad en tweak gør, langt tryk på det og en tutorial vil dukke op.</string>
    <string name="select_apps">Vælg apps</string>
    <string name="enable_assistant_shortcuts">Assistent genveje</string>
    <string name="patch_custom_apps">tilpassede apps</string>
    <string name="disable_speed_limitations">begrænsning af tryk</string>
    <string name="unlimited_scrolling_when_driving">hastighedsbegrænsning</string>
    <string name="message_auto_read">Message auto-read</string>
    <string name="splash">Denne app kan ændre Android Auto adfærd og omgå nogle sikkerhedsfunktioner, som Google har implementeret i Android Auto.\n
Ved at bruge denne software accepterer du, at DIN og KUN DIG, alene er ansvarlige for eventuelle konsekvenser, der kan føre til ændringer af sikkerhedselementer, såsom skader på dig selv og/eller andre skader på ejendom, tab af liv.\n
Under ingen omstændigheder er forfatteren af denne app ansvarlig for dens anvendelse</string>
    <string name="proceed">Jeg forstår</string>
    <string name="navigation_at_start">Navigation ved start</string>
    <string name="statb_opaque_string">Tving Ugennemsigtig Statuslinje</string>
    <string name="battery_outline_string">batterisparefunktion skitse</string>
    <string name="legend">Status Legend:\n
GREEN= Patch anvendt\n
YELLOW= Genstart er nødvendig for at anvende patch\n
RED= Patch anvendes ikke\n</string>
    <string name="set_notification_duration_to">Notifikationens varighed</string>
    <string name="base_no_ws">Widescreen</string>
    <string name="force_widescreen_text">Tving Widescreen</string>
    <string name="media_notification_duration_to">Medie notifikations varighed til</string>
    <string name="bluetooth_auto_connect">Bluetooth auto-forbindelse</string>
    <string name="tutorial_nospeed">Denne tweak vil gøre Android Auto tror, at bilen er på 0 hastighed. Som et resultat, Android Auto vil altid vise forhåndsvisning af meddelelser. This tweak does not apply to keyboard or first configuration of Android Auto. (Automatic Copy).</string>
    <string name="tutorial_sixtap">Denne tweak vil tilsidesætte grænsen på 6 tryk på Android Auto og vil gøre ubegrænset browsing af indhold altid muligt.</string>
    <string name="tutorial_shortcuts">Denne tweak vil låse op for den nye Assistent Genveje funktion. Når aktiveret, kan du gå i Android Auto indstillinger, og i afsnittet Tilpas launcher kan du begynde at tilføje genveje til Google Assistant kommandoer</string>
    <string name="tutorial_startup">Denne tweak vil tilsidesætte standardadfærden i Android Automatisk åbning af en navigationsapp ved start og vil gøre Android Auto starte på launcher.\n
I nogle tilfælde vil denne tweak deaktivere automatisk start af musik. En kendt løsning er at deaktivere og genaktivere indstillingen i Android Auto indstillinger.\n
DET IKKE BEVARES TIL AT SØGE EN SPECIFIK APP TIL AT START FØRST.</string>
    <string name="tutorial_widescreen">Denne tweak vil tvinge Android Auto i widescreen tilstand.</string>
    <string name="tutorial_no_widescreen">Denne tweak vil tvinge Android Auto i ingen widescreen tilstand.</string>
    <string name="tutorial_autoplay_message">This tweak enables the possibility to set whether Android Auto must read the incoming messages or not. Android Auto 8.3 or superior is required.</string>
    <string name="tutorial_statusbar_opaque">Denne tweak vil gøre statuslinjen altid sort.</string>
    <string name="tutorial_battery_outline">Denne tweak vil forhindre batteri-ikonet med den røde omrids når batteribesparelse er tændt.</string>
    <string name="tutorial_hun">Denne tweak lader dig indstille en brugerdefineret varighed for hoveder op meddelelser</string>
    <string name="tutorial_media_hun">Denne tweak lader dig indstille en brugerdefineret varighed for medier meddelelser i navigationsbjælken til op til 15 minutter.</string>
    <string name="tutorial_bluetooth">Denne tweak bør forhindre Bluetooth i at tænde, når Android Auto er tilsluttet. Denne tweak virker ikke, hvis Bluetooth allerede er tændt.</string>
    <string name="tutorial_patchapps">Denne tweak vil gøre det muligt for tredjeparts-apps lavet specifikt med Android Auto brugerdefinerede SDK til at arbejde på Android Auto.\n
Hvis du er bekendt med AA Phenotype Patcher, denne tweak er stort set identisk med det.\n
Det er ikke muligt at tilføje bare enhver app til Android Auto, men det er muligt at lappe sideloaded apps MADE TIL ANDROID AUTO til at arbejde i biler.</string>
    <string name="multi_display_string">Multi Skærm</string>
    <string name="tutorial_multidisplay">Dette er en skjult funktion inde i Android Auto-, der vil slå den anden plads i widescreen tilstand til en reel anden skærm, der er helt taget af en seond aktivitet. Google Maps vil vise et fuldt kort med navigationsstatus, musik og telefoner vil tage det fulde rum.\n
Denne tilstand aktiverer desuden en anden funktion, der vil slå telefonens skærm til i et andet display for navigation i Android Auto.\n
Indstillinger for tweaking af denne funktion vil være tilgængelige i Android Autostartskærm.\n
Tilsyneladende understøtter kun Google Maps i øjeblikket denne tilstand.\n
Denne funktion er sandsynligvis under udvikling og kunne potentielt ikke fungere efter hensigten.\n
Android Auto 5.8 eller overlegen er påkrævet.</string>
    <string name="battery_warning">Advarsel om strømsparetilstand</string>
    <string name="tutorial_battery_saver_warning">Denne tweak vil forhindre Android Auto i at give popup advarsler, når batterisparetilstand er tændt</string>
    <string name="disable_tweak_string">Deaktiver\u0020</string>
    <string name="enable_tweak_string">Aktiver\u0020</string>
    <string name="re_enable_tweak_string">Genaktiver\u0020</string>
    <string name="copy_log">Kopier log</string>
    <string name="about">Om</string>
    <string name="revert_everything">Fortryd alt</string>
    <string name="force_disable_tweak">Gennemtving Deaktivér\u0020</string>
    <string name="reset_tweak">Reset\u0020</string>
    <string name="force_widescreen_warning">Tving widescreen er blevet deaktiveret automatisk</string>
    <string name="force_disable_widescreen_warning">Gennemtving deaktivere widescreen er automatisk deaktiveret</string>
    <string name="set_value">Indstil\u0020</string>
    <string name="reboot_to_apply">REBOOT FOR AT ANVENDE</string>
    <string name="warning_title">ADVARSEL</string>
    <string name="unpatch">Frigør\u0020</string>
    <string name="patch_app">Patch\u0020</string>
    <string name="default_string">\u0020Default</string>
    <string name="app_list_label">Apps List</string>
    <string name="translators_button">Translated by</string>
    <string name="custom_wallpapers">Wallpapers</string>
    <string name="tutorial_wallpapers">This tweak will activate the new built in wallpaper changer in Android Auto. Android Auto 5.8 or superior is required.\nWARNING: If you are a user of Wallpapers For Android Auto, you will need to update it to at least version 3.0, otherwise this tweak will break Wallpapers For Android Auto functionality.</string>
    <string name="tutorial_dark_mode">Starting from December 2020, Google reverted a behaviour that happened since Android 10. Previously, the light/dark mode on Android Auto followed the light/dark mode on the phone and vice versa. This meant that switching the phone to dark mode had effect on the car, or if the phone was in dark mode and the car had lights off it used to switch on the light theme on the phone.\n However, since this feature of \"independent\" dark mode was introduced, users with Aftermarket headunits have no way to switch to dark mode anymore without actually wiring the stereo to the car\'s lights.\n This tweak makes sure that night mode is again dependent from phone and switching light/dark mode on phone will have its effects on cars too.</string>
    <string name="dark_mode_tweak">independent dark mode</string>
    <string name="telemetry_string">telemetry</string>
    <string name="tutorial_telemetry">It\'s no mystery that Google logs a lot of data about us. This tweak will make so that Google Play Services will stop a lot of tracking and logging activity.\n
WARNING: This tweak has not been extensively tested and could potentially break Android Auto. If you find out that this tweak breaks Android Auto, please open an issue on GitHub.</string>
    <string name="reboot_prompt">Reboot phone now?</string>
    <string name="rebooting_action">Rebooting…</string>
    <string name="added_app_action">"Added: "</string>
    <string name="removed_app_action">Removed\u0020</string>
    <string name="root_access_warning">Root access denied. Please allow root access.</string>
    <string name="revert_everything_dialog">Do you want to revert everything? Please manually restart the app after doing so</string>
    <string name="calendar_tweak">Set %1$s visible days in calendar</string>
    <string name="calendar_tweak_single">Set %1$s visible day in calendar</string>
    <string name="tutorial_calendar_tweak">This tweak will make so that calendar app into Android Auto can show more days than just one. Please note that even increasing the number of days, it\'s still not obviously possible to distinguish which day you are viewing the events of. Android Auto will just show how many events are set in one day and it won\'t show which day it is.</string>
    <string name="choose_apps_warning">Choose apps to whitelist</string>
    <string name="log_first_line">LOG:\n</string>
    <string name="menu_aa_settings">Open Android Auto settings</string>
    <string name="not_enabled_warning">Android Auto is not enabled</string>
    <string name="not_installed_warning">Android Auto is not installed</string>
    <string name="currently_set">"Currently set: "</string>
    <string name="no_accounts_warning">AA AIO TWEAKER could not find any account in Google Play Services database. This can be caused by several different things such as:\n • Device that is mostly not connected to internet\n • Fresh install of the phone\n • Corrupted Google Play Services database\n • Removal of Google account(s) from the phone\n • Cleared datas of Google Play Services\n\nIn this scenario, AA AIO TWEAKER will FAIL to work properly. If you recently removed a Google account or cleared Google Play Services datas, please keep the phone connected to internet and let it build the Google Play Services database fully. This might take several hours, in some cases also days.\n\nIf you are not in one of the above conditions, please open a issue on GitHub.</string>
    <string name="tweak_loading">Applying the tweak...</string>
    <string name="loading">Loading, please wait...</string>
    <string name="tutorial_bitrate">This tweak will increase or decrease video bitrate according to the multiplier set (up to 2.0x). Increasing the bitrate (more than 1.0x) will mean that more datas will be streamed to the car and quality of video streaming could be improved in visual quality, however it might cause instability. Decreasing the bitrate (less than 1.0x) will compress the stream to the car and quality will be decreased, but it will result in a more reliable and fast connection.</string>
    <string name="set_wifi_tweak">wifi bitrate to</string>
    <string name="set_usb_bitrate">USB bitrate to</string>
    <string name="choose_value_first">Choose a value first</string>
    <string name="open_issue_button">Open Issue</string>
    <string name="error_generic">The command was not successful. Please wait some minutes and try again. If problem is still ongoing, please open a issue on GitHub</string>
    <string name="tutorial_alphajump">This tweak will activate a new (and hidden) redesign that changes how lists can be browsed with letters. Instead of the A-Z button at the top, the button will appear on the scrollbar when there\'s no scroll happening and you won\'t be forced to go to top to browse with letters again.</string>
    <string name="alpha_jump_tweak">new alphabet jump</string>
    <string name="choose_accounts">Choose accounts</string>
    <string name="use_all">Use all (EXPERIMENTAL)</string>
    <string name="copied_pastebin">A link to the log has been created and copied to clipboard</string>
    <string name="log_copied">Log has been copied</string>
    <string name="new_version_available">New Version available</string>
    <string name="go_to_new_version">A new version of AA AIO TWEAKER (version %1$s) is available on GitHub. Do you want to download it now?</string>
    <string name="go_to_download">Go to download</string>
    <string name="ignore_for_now">Ignorer for nu</string>
    <string name="many_accounts_warning">AA AIO TWEAKER fundet et stort antal (%1$s) af Google-konti, der er gemt i enheden.\nDette kan have en negativ indvirkning på succesen af lappe processen og AA AIO TWEAKER kan mislykkes.\nDu kan enten vælge den eller de konti, som du oftest bruger med Google Play-tjenester, til at anvende programrettelsen på bare dem (2 eller mindre anbefales) eller aktivere en eksperimentel tilstand, der skal lappe alle konti.\nBEMÆRK at eksperimentelle tilstand kan forårsage nogle nedbrud på telefonen, mens patch kører.</string>
    <string name="dark_switch_tweak">indstillingen dag/nat</string>
    <string name="tutorial_assistant_suggestions">This tweak will activate a new feature that adds some quick shortcuts to Assistant actions on top of home screen.</string>
    <string name="remove_paired_car">Fjern en parret bil</string>
    <string name="choose_cars">Vælg biler</string>
    <string name="tutorial_carremover">Vidste du, at du kun kan fjerne alle de parrede biler fra Android Auto og du kan ikke fjerne bare én ad gangen? Denne indstilling vil redde dig, hvis du ønsker at slette en bil fra Android Auto, bare vælge, hvilke biler du ønsker, og det/de vil blive fjernet.</string>
    <string name="coolwalk_daynight_tweak">Light/Dark Coolwalk</string>
    <string name="coolwalk_daynight_tutorial">This tweak will activate day/night mode for Coolwalk mode. Looks kind of broken right now and can\'t handle switch very well.</string>
    <string name="custom_hotseat_option">Custom seating option</string>
    <string name="tutorial_coolwalk">This tweak will activate a new design in Android Auto (codename Coolwalk) that can be toggled in Android Auto\'s settings and that tweaks a bit the appearance on smaller screens. This design features a always on side panel and some different graphics. This feature is in early stage at the moment. Android Auto 6.9 or superior is required.</string>
    <string name="coolwalk_tweak">Coolwalk design</string>
    <string name="tutorial_focus_settings">This tweak will activate a new options in Android Auto settings to manually customize whether Android Auto must be launched as soon as you connect your phone with the car. Android Auto 6.8 or superior is required.</string>
    <string name="focus_tweak">Focus settings</string>
    <string name="assistant_tips">Assistant tips</string>
    <string name="tutorial_mirroring_app">This tweak will enable Assistant Tips on the top of the home screen for most used actions. Android Auto 8.2 or superior is required.</string>
    <string name="decline_message_tweak">Decline with message</string>
    <string name="tutorial_decline_message">This tweak will enable the possibility to decline an incoming call with SMS (with Google Assistant).</string>
    <string name="section_one">General tweaks</string>
    <string name="section_two">Screen setup tweaks</string>
    <string name="section_three">Appearance tweaks</string>
    <string name="section_four">Video quality settings</string>
    <string name="section_five">Pre-activate features</string>
    <string name="restricted_coolwalk">\nThis option will only work with Coolwalk enabled.</string>
    <string name="warning_patch_apps">Warning! This operation will ERASE ALL THE DATA from the selected app(s). Please make sure you have a backup of the data. Do you want to proceed anyways?</string>
    <string name="tappable_progress">New progress bar</string>
    <string name="tappable_progress_tutorial">Finally we are gaining a touchable progress bar for what\'s playing on Android Auto. Yes, we can seek through the current track Requires Android Auto 8.3 or superior.</string>
    <string name="uxprototype_tutorial">All this tweak does is basically creates a free shortcut on the home page to open a web page. It involves an Easter egg hidden in Android Auto released on 1st of April 2022. Activate \"Developer mode\" in \"Developer settings\" under \"Application mode\". It\'s the only way to have an actual fullscreen app on Android Auto right now. WARNING: Not exitable, use this if you only plan on using this on your car. There\'s no back button either.</string>
    <string name="uxprototype_dialog">Enter a valid full URL</string>
    <string name="uxprototype_tweak">Custom shortcut</string>
    <string name="tutorial_new_seekbar">"This tweak enables a movable seekbar for media apps."</string>
    <string name="tutorial_materialyou">"This tweak enables material you style for the Android Auto's settings on the phone. This properly works only on Android Auto 8.8&gt; as tested"</string>
    <string name="tutorial_nocoolwalk">Are you absolutely hating Coolwalk? This tweak is for you.</string>
    <string name="portrait_layout">Force vertical layout</string>
    <string name="tutorial_portrait">This tweak will force the portrait layout of Android Auto with dashboard on the bottom.</string>
    <string name="inertial_scroll_tweak">Inertial scroll</string>
    <string name="tutorial_inertial_scroll">This tweak will override the default scrolling behaviour of Android Auto making so that it doesn\'t stop page by page.</string>
</resources>
